## Brianley99@gmail.com 6197512529

### 92119, San Diego United States

#### Skills

- Campaign Management
- Data Transcription
- Microsoft Office
- Data Management
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- Scripting Languages: Javascript, Python
- Software Deployment
- Adobe Software
- Time Management

## **Education And Training**

07/2017

High School Diploma: Chula Vista High School Chula Vista

## Languages

**English, Spanish**: First Language

# Brian N. Ley

## Summary

Detailed Data Entry Clerk with experience inputting and organizing data in various software and applications. Extensively trained in transcription, word processing and spreadsheets. Organized individual recognized for transposing large amounts of data with accuracy and speed.

## Experience

#### Spec-Build Systems - General Laborer

San Diego

11/2021 - Current

- Read plans, instructions or specifications to determine work activities.
- Performed repetitive assembly tasks with hand and power tools and automated equipment.
- Operated pallet jacks and forklifts to load and unload supplies and materials.

#### **Ajinomoto Foods - Machine Operator**

San Diego

02/2021 - 08/2021

- Documented daily production data and submitted accurate time logs to keep management up-to-date.
- Assigned tasks to employees and monitored productivity, performance and task completion.
- Completed written reports of problems and necessary repairs to forward to management and maintenance personnel.
- Set up machines for various jobs to maintain compliance with manufacturing thresholds and waste reduction initiatives.

#### **Aspire - Account Manager**

San Diego

10/2019 - 03/2020

- Met, engaged and pursued customers through networking, referrals and marketing.
- Input data into CRM system to manage existing portfolios and potential leads.
- Researched competitors and customer business models for sales strategy development.
- Negotiated product pricing, freight rates and delivery and payment terms to beat competition and elevate client retention.